Chandler: I'm moving out, so you're
in charge of paying the rent.
Joey: When's it due?
Chandler: On the first.
Joey: And that's every month?
Chandler: No, just the months
you want to live here.
Chandler: Okay, here's the phone bill.
Joey: Oh, my God!
Chandler: That's our phone number.
Chandler: I know I kind of sprung this
me-moving-out-on-you thing.
Chandler: Why don't I cover you for a while?
Joey: No way!
Joey: Joey Tribbiani does not
take charity...
Joey: ...anymore.
Chandler: It's not charity, Joe.
Joey: Forget it.
Joey: Thanks, but I'm done
taking money from you.
Joey: I can take care of myself.
What's next? Come on.
Chandler: Here's the electric bill.
Joey: This is how much we pay for electric?
Chandler: -Well, yeah.
Chandler: So we'll do
the rest of the bills later, then?
Phoebe: Will Joey have to give up
the apartment?
Chandler: I offered him money,
but he wouldn't take it.
Phoebe: How much does he need?
Chandler: $1500 would cover him
for a few months...
Chandler: ...but I have to trick him into
taking it so I don't hurt his pride.
Phoebe: Why don't you hire him as an actor?
Phoebe: You could have him dress up
and put on skits whenever you want.
Chandler: Well, that would help the pride thing.
Chandler: Wow, you look great! Do you wanna
move in with me tomorrow?
Chandler: Any plans for tonight?
Monica: Instead of being sad on my
last night with Rachel...
Monica: ...we're going out to celebrate
Rachel's moving in with Phoebe.
Phoebe: And also my birthday.
Monica: It's not your birthday.
Phoebe: What a mean thing to say! I'd never
tell you it wasn't your birthday.
Phoebe: You guys have anything planned
for the big last night?
Chandler: Instead of just hanging out,
we figure we'd do nothing.
Ross: Knicks' season opener tonight.
I thought you'd come and watch it.
Joey: I don't know, Ross.
Joey: Not if you talk about how you gave up
basketball to become a paleontologist.
Ross: I did give up a career in basketball
to become a paleontologist!
Rachel: Pheebs--
Monica: You're not dressed yet?
Monica: We're supposed to start having fun
in 15 minutes!
Rachel: And clearly, not a minute sooner.
Monica: You are packed, though, right?
Please tell me you're packed?
Rachel: Of course I'm packed.
Monica, relax.
Rachel: I wanted to ask Phoebe
what I should wear.
Phoebe: My God, I can't get a minute of peace.
Phoebe: Oh, my God!
Phoebe: Monica's just gonna kill you.
Rachel: I know.
Phoebe: What you're wearing is fine
for that.
Monica: You're not packed!
Monica: You're not packed even a little bit!
Rachel: Surprise!
Rachel: Don't get mad,
because this is what happened.
Rachel: I started packing,
then I realized, "What am I doing?"
Rachel: I am lousy at packing, right?
Rachel: But you love packing!
Rachel: So as a gift to you
on our last night... .
Monica: I'll be coordinator!
Monica: Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
I didn't get you anything.
Monica: Everybody has to help.
Phoebe, can you help?
Phoebe: I have plans.
Monica: You have plans with us.
Phoebe: That's right.
Monica: Chandler can make boxes, Ross can
wrap, and Joey can lift.
Monica: Tell the guys
they have to help out.
Monica: My God, thank you!
Phoebe: Monica's gonna make you pack!
She's got jobs for everyone!
Phoebe: Now, it's too late for me,
but save yourselves!
Monica: The movers will be here in 11 hours.
Rachel hasn't packed.
Monica: Now, everybody has to help.
Chandler--
Chandler: I have plans with Joey.
Monica: You said you were doing nothing.
Chandler: Yes, but for the last time.
Monica: Fine. Now, Ross--
Ross: I can't do it.
Monica: Why not?
Joey: Don't you have Ben?
Ross: Because I have Ben!
Monica: It's almost past his bedtime.
Where is he?
Chandler: He's at a dinner party.
Monica: He's really coming?
I can see in your apartment.
Ross: Of course he is. What?
Ross: You think I'd use my son as an excuse?
Ross: What kind of father do you think I am?
Monica: All right. Sorry.
Ross: I gotta go make a fake Ben.
Joey: Here it is.
Joey: Our last pizzas together as roommates.
Chandler: I wish I knew that.
I ordered Chinese.
Joey: Well, that's okay.
Joey: In a way it's kind of nice.
You know?
Joey: Our last dinner together. Me,
bringing the food of my ancestors...
Chandler: ...you, the food of yours!
I had an idea for what to do
on our last night.
Chandler: What do you say we play a little
foosball for money?
Joey: Are you crazy? You haven't beaten me
since my injury-plagued '97 season.
Joey: It'd be easier to give me your money.
Chandler: Yes, it would.
Chandler: What do you say to $50?
Joey: You're on.
Chandler: Okay, let's play.
Chandler: The big game. Italy versus...
Chandler: ...China, apparently.